根据BDRip TLF版本重新调整时间轴
by：forgetted@tlf
原字幕出处：CHD
本字幕仅供学习交流
切勿用于商业用途
法则1：一个人的原则 准则 还是诚心 都会成为一种法则
我打赌你的脑子里满是问题
Oh, I bet you got a lot of questions
rattling around in your head.
－这活有多少钱？
－大约在35－50万之间
-How much money in the case?
-Anywhere between 350 and half a mil.
－你要多少，瓦尔？
－我们五五分。
-And how much do you need, Val?
-We split it 50-50.
－那是多少？
－13万
-How much?
-130 grand.
－我们星期五行动
－那还不够
-We'll hit them on Friday.
-It's not enough.
－你要多少，瓦尔？
－五五分。
-And how much do you need, Val?
- We split it 50-50.
－这是我的钱
－没错，好吧，我少点
-It's my money.
-Yeah, well, I'm up short.
我拿七成，我要还钱
My 70 grand, I want it back.
－你拿6成
－7成
-60 short.
-70.
7成，瓦尔。我要7万，你个混蛋
70, Val. It's 70 grand.
70, you dumb bastards.
帮帮忙吧
Help the homeless.
帮帮无家可归的人
这些只是些小钱，你们就不能给大点吗？
Oh, that's small change. Why don't
you give me some big change?
行行好，给大点
Give a guy a break. What do you say?
给多点。
Come on, now.
哈，谢谢你，伙计
嗨，你他妈的！
Oh, thanks, man. Oh...
Hey, what the fuck!
你...
What are you...
你个婊子养的!
Son of a... Motherfucker!
- 多少钱？
- 两块九毛八
-What do I owe you?
-$2.98.
浑蛋 我的香烟!
Son of a... Hey! Hey, my cigarettes!
抱歉，对不起
Oh! Sorry, sir. Pardon me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
一百, 两百, 三百.
$100, $200, $300.
祝您愉快，强森先生
Have a nice day, Mr. Johnson.
非常合身，先生
Excellent fit, sir.
您要怎么付钱？
And how will you be paying?
这些手表给你当九百
Yeah, I'll give you $900 for this.
给我看看那把马格南手枪
Let me see that Magnum.
嗯.就这个.
That's it.
五百块加那把枪
$500 and the gun.
- 我要看看你的身份证明
- 没问题.
-I'll need to see some lD.
-Of course.
抱歉，强森先生
这张信用卡无效了
I'm sorry, Mr. Johnson.
This card's been canceled.
不可能.
lmpossible.
我都试过两次了.
Well, I tried it twice.
- 您可以用别的支付吗?
- 再试一次.
-Do you have another form of payment?
-Try it again.
波特, 你没死.
Porter, you're not dead.
瓦尔呢?
Where's Val?
走了. 都走了2个月了.
Gone. Moved out two months ago.
- 他去哪里了?
- 不知道.
-Where?
-Don't know.
- 那谁给你付租金?
- 瓦尔.
-Who's paying your rent?
-Val.
- 哦?
- 我猜大概是一次性付清了.
-Why?
-Payoff, I guess.
什么?你猜?你不知道?
What, you guess? You don't know?
靠!你他妈的有胆回来
Damn it! You've got a fucking lot
of nerve coming around here
还趾高气扬的,怎么,你带了个婊子一块是吧?
all fucking high and mighty. What,
you bring your whore with you, did you?
- 不.
- 看着!
-No, no, no.
-Look at it!
你给我看看.
看看我们之前的时候,宝贝.
Look, see. Look at that.
That's before we met, baby.
给我想想.
Think about it.
哦, 天啊.
Oh, God.
- 你想怎么样,波特?
- 我要把我的钱要回来.
-So, what are you gonna do, Porter?
-I'm gonna get my money back.
你看,我只好来找你了
You mean, what am I gonna do to you.
这由你决定
Well, that depends on you.
瓦尔在哪?
Where's Val?
我告诉过你,我不知道
I told you, I don't know.
他不是老早就有财团了吗
Did he ever buy his way back
into the syndicate?
嗯
Yeah.
你是怎么从他那里拿钱的?
How do you get your payoffs?
送信的,一开始每月都投个带现金的信封
A messenger, first of every month,
leaves an envelope with cash in it.
她是谁?在照片里的那个
So, who was she, anyway?
That girl in the picture.
我出狱的时候遇见她
I met her when I got out of prison.
我利用了她,本想在事做完之后确保她安全
I used to drive her,
keep her safe while she worked.
你算什么?拉皮条的?
What were you, her pimp?
不.
No, no.
我们一起为那个B工作过
We both worked for that asshole.
现在不行
Not now.
嗯
Yeah.
你没有毒瘾
You're cleaning up.
是.
No.
瓦尔想和你通话.
Val still wants to talk to you.
对不起,亲爱的.
Sorry, babe.
我要让他再打给你吗?
Shall I tell him to call back again?
不,我来吧.
No, I'll talk to him.
叫他别烦我
Shut him up, anyway.
瓦尔.
Val.
啊,老样子,你呢?
Yeah, same as always. You?
嗯,好,很好.
Yeah, good, good.
什么?你现在在那?
Why? You there now?
别怕，他们觉得白人都一个样
Well, don't sweat it, Val.
I mean, we all look alike to them.
姓周的手下，同一批人
Same crew. The Chows.
一周两次, 周二和周五.
Twice a week, Tuesday and Friday.
周二和周五中午，同一条路线
Always between 1 1 :00 and 1 2:00,
always the same route.
华人洗“钱”店
Chinese money laundering.
- 皮箱里有多少钱？?
- 三十五万到五十万.
-How much money in the case?
-Anywhere between 350 and half a mil.
- 你需要多少?
- 我们平分.
-And how much do you need, Val?
-We split it 50-50.
我是指你需要多少才能回去
No, I mean, how much do you need to,
you know, buy your way back?
重回组织.多少？
lnto the syndicate. How much?
- 你是说黑道？
- 对啦
-You mean the outfit?
-Whatever.
天啊，你什么都知道
Jesus, you know everything.
嗨，小妹妹
Hi, sweetie.
十三万
1 30 grand.
漂亮的是...他们不会报警，
The beauty of the Chows
is they won't go to the cops.
只能吃闷亏,他们也不会心痛
They keep everything in-house,
and they don't feel pain the way we do.
这些人有什么不对劲？
You notice anything
about those guys, Val?
都是狠角色
They look nasty.
没准都是他妈的功夫高手
Probably all kung fu motherfuckers.
- 怎么？我遗漏了什么？
- 他们没系安全带
-Why? Did I miss something?
-They weren't wearing their seat belts.
星期五下手
We'll hit them on Friday.
Hubba, hubba, hubba.
你看他.
Looky here.
被撞得很爽吧？
How's that vinyl taste?
瓦尔!
Val!
干嘛？
What?
那家伙怎么扁都扁不死
The problem with kicking
the Chows' asses,
一小时后你还想再来一次
an hour later you wanna do it again.
Huh?
十四万
140 grand.
各分十四万
140 apiece.
总共
Total.
总共？
Total?
这只有7万?
That's... That's what? That's 70 grand?
-对我根本就不够
-我够了
-That's not enough.
-lt is for me.
我要休息几个月
袋子交给你，亲爱的
I'm taking the next few months off.
Here's the bag, baby.
我还缺...
Yeah, well, I'm up short.
六万块钱. 那些臭家伙!
60 short. Fucking slants!
早该礼拜二下手，可恶！
Should've hit them Tuesday. Fuck!
这一笔干得干净俐落
还抢了一大笔钱
We got away clean
and got something to show for it.
知足常乐，第一条规矩,瓦尔
Always be grateful for what you get.
Rule number one, Val.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊...第一条规矩
Yeah. Rule number one.
干嘛？
What?
没事了
Everything's cool.
只是钱不够
It's just not enough, all right?
钱永远都不够，瓦尔
It never is, Val.
亲爱的，把钱放车上
Hey, baby, just put the money
in the car, will you?
难以想像...我们应该
I can't fucking believe it. We should...
波特，你知道吗？
You know... You know what?
You know what, Porter?
很好笑. 你会笑死
This is funny. This'll kill you.
我早就知道是十四万
It's always $140,000.
应该有人颁我哲学博士头衔
Someone ought to give me a PhD.
你...
You...
妈的!
Shit!
天, 林恩,
等我先躲开好吗？
Jesus, Lynn,
wait till I'm out of the fucking way!
没事了，宝贝
Okay, everything's cool, baby.
Oh! Oh!
你很棒，你很棒
You were great. You were great.
没事了，枪给我
Everything's cool. Give me the... Okay.
好吧，枪还是你拿着
Okay, okay, keep the gun.
结束了，没事了
That's it. Everything's cool.
都照计划进行
Just like we planned. Come on.
振作点，可不要精神崩溃
Don't fall apart on me now.
来吧
There we go.
我打赌你的脑子里满是问题
Oh, I bet you got a lot of questions
rattling around in your head.
我也不晓得,宝贝
I don't know, pally.
太太会对情人醋劲那么大
I guess wives get funny
when it comes to girlfriends, huh?
什么？
What?
我听不清楚
I didn't get that.
是你要的哦
You got it.
波特小姐，我没闲工夫等
Come on, Miss Porter,
I don't have all day!
波特小姐在吗？
ls... Is Miss Porter here?
是波特太太
Mrs. Porter.
随便啦
Yeah, whatever.
王八蛋!
You motherfucker!
起来，转过去
Get up, turn around.
起来
Come on. Get up. Come on.
这是什么？
What have we got here, huh?
- 这里有多少钱？
- 两千
-How much in here, huh?
-There's two grand.
这是什么？
What's in here?
氦? 你想会是什么？是海洛因!
Helium. What the fuck you think it is?
It's heroin.
Oh, fuck!
惨了，惨了
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
操!
Fuck!
瓦尔雷斯尼克
Val Resnick.
他在哪？
Where is he?
你想知道吗？
You wanna know where he is?
他在这儿，你看.操你.
He's right here. Look. Look. Fuck you.
答错了
Wrong answer.
你这混蛋
Shit! You motherfucker!
- 该死!
- 瓦尔雷斯尼克.
-Fuck!
-Val Resnick.
从来没听过,靠
I never heard of him, man. Fuck.
钱和毒品哪儿来的？
Where'd you get the envelope
and the shit?
拜托，他们会杀了我
Come on, man,
they're gonna fucking kill me.
他们会把我杀了
They're gonna kill me, man.
你以为我不敢？
What do you think I'm gonna do?
想活就快说
Worry about me.
别这样，好啦...好啦...
Oh, come on. Okay.
好, 好, 好.
Okay, okay, okay.
史泰曼...亚瑟史泰曼那烂人
Stegman... Stegman, man.
Arthur fucking Stegman. Okay?
他在哪儿？
Where is he?
南区计程车行
Southend Taxi.
费洛嘉路
Farragut Road, man.
谢了
Thanks.
不客气
You're welcome.
我找亚瑟史泰曼
I'm looking for Arthur Stegman.
他不在，我能效劳吗？
He ain't here.
Something I can help you with?
不，你不能，他人呢？
No, you can't. Where is he?
不晓得，他不在
I don't know. He ain't here.
猜猜看
Take a guess.
什么？
What?
猜猜看他会在哪里
Take a guess about where he is.
他在家吗？
Is he at home?
你为啥不找个地方打手枪?
Why don't you go fuck yourself?
好,开始
All right, here we go.
快点掷, 我赢了!
Hey, come on, roll it!
- 等下,那是我的!
- 这不是你的,伙计.
-Wait a minute. That was mine!
-lt was not yours, man.
我赢了
I get one more shot.
有人要找你
There's somebody here to see you.
我找史泰曼
I'm looking for Stegman.
你是什么人？
Who the hell are you?
我是波特
I'm Porter.
波特，看起来你...
犯了攻击罪
Well, Porter,
that looks like assault to me.
看起来波特也会拒捕
Porter looks to me like the kind
that likes to resist arrest.
-Hey!
-Whoa!
可恶，别在这里开枪
Fuck, no! Not in here.
伙计们.他只是有话要说
Jesus, guys, he just... He wants to talk.
对吧？ 对不对？
Am I right? Did I call it?
你是史泰曼吗？
Are you Stegman?
也许是. 你要什么？
Maybe. What do you want?
你手下的货没送成
Your boy didn't make his delivery.
天啊
Jesus.
哈,亚瑟.
Whoa, Artie.
嘿,别担心这个
我们出去谈谈好吗
Hey, listen, don't worry about it.
Why don't we talk outside?
亚瑟，你是毒贩？
Artie, you're a dealer?
别多管闲事，好吗？
Just forget about it, all right?
还有别碰我的钱
And don't touch my money, either.
- 走吧
- 这是海洛因?
-Come on. Let's...
-This is heroin?
- 这是海洛因
- 伙计们...
-This is heroin.
-Guys, just...
别担心，轻松一点
咱们出去谈
Don't worry about it, all right?
Just take it easy. Let's talk. Come on.
看什么看？玩你的牌
What are you guys looking at?
Play your game.
你想把血都滴到我的睡椅上吗?
走吧. 走吧.
And you're bleeding all over my couch.
Come on, you. Come on.
史泰曼在瞒着我们
Steggie's been holding out on us.
我去查一查
I'll check it out.
瓦尔雷斯尼克
Val Resnick.
- 他怎样？
- 他在哪？
-What about him?
-You're gonna tell me where he is.
不行，就算我知道也不会说
No. No. Even if I knew,
the answer would still be no.
你在哪里碰到送货小弟？
Now, where'd you meet up
with my delivery boy?
送货的地方
At his drop.
他死了？
Is he dead?
没有，不过女的死了，吸毒过量
No, but she is. OD'd on that crap
you've been sending her.
又怎样？
So?
- 关你什么事？
- 我是她先生
-What do you care?
-I'm her husband.
你不会杀我吧？
You're not gonna fucking kill me,
are you?
在孩子面前不会
Not in front of these kids.
他人呢？
Where is he?
不知道
I don't know.
是真的
That's the truth.
货是昨晚才送给我的
You see, this stuff gets delivered to me,
too, you know. Last night.
下个月才会再联络
And I won't see anyone again
till next month.
干嘛这么麻烦？
Why all the trouble?
他怕那女的
Well, he's afraid of the girl.
我是说... 波特太太
You know, I mean, of... Of Mrs. Porter.
我知道的就这么多
Look, I don't know nothing
about this, okay?
其他我都不知道
I know Val from the old days.
三个月前他找到我,要我帮忙
Three months ago he shows up,
asks me to do him a favor.
我每月多赚一千，何乐不为？
I make an extra grand a month,
so I figure, what the hell, right?
你干嘛要威胁要杀我？
Now you come around
threatening to kill me?
相信我,
我又不是瓦尔的死党
Believe me,
that much a buddy of Val's, I am not.
我只知道他还在城里
He's in the city. That's it.
That's all I know.
- 我得进去了
- 你怎么知道他在？
-I got a game going on in here.
-How do you know that?
他说的.
He said so.
- 几时？
- 哦
-When?
-When he... Then.
他来我这里时
When he came around.
跟我说他又回到黑帮
Said that he squared himself
with the syndicate.
这次肯定能吃香喝辣
Said he was back in the big time.
他很兴奋
Back for good. He was very excited.
你跟他说波特也回来了
Well, you tell him
that Porter is back, too,
来跟他要钱
波特要讨回他的钱
and he wants his money,
Porter wants his money.
否则我会来找你
Or I'll come back here
and pay you a visit
- 等孩子不在的时候
- 啊...
-when these kids are not around.
-Well...
我该几时跟他说？
When would I tell him this?
请讲.
Talk to me.
有位小姐找你，她叫珀尔.
There's a young lady to see you, sir.
Her name is Pearl.
她有两种不良嗜好
She's got two very bad habits.
现在,
我只对其中一种有兴趣
Right now,
I'm only interested in one of them.
让她上来.
Send her up.
718室, 小姐. 请上去.
Apartment 71 8, ma'am. Go right on up.
- 叫她上来，搞什么？
- 瓦尔,我是哈斯卡.
-Send her up. What's the problem?
-Hey, Val, it's Haskell.
抱歉打扰你,不过我想..
Sorry to be calling you at home,
but I thought...
别道歉，不要烦我
Don't be sorry, sweetie. Just don't call.
我想,这应该是大事.
Well, I thought it might be important.
南区计程车行的小子来电.
I got a call from a cab guy
out in the south end.
- 什么事？
- 史泰曼那小子.
-What is it?
-Well, it's this guy, Stegman.
可恶，等一下
Shit. Hold on a second.
跪下来，婊子
我要好好教训你
On your knees, bitch.
I want satisfaction.
我在讲电话，珀尔
I'm on the phone, Pearl.
叫我珀尔夫人，臭狗屎
That's Mistress Pearl,
you piece of dog shit.
我正在讲电话
I'm on the fucking phone!
有屁快放
Make it quick, huh?
史泰曼打电话来
他很紧张
So, anyhow, this guy Stegman called.
He sounded all nervous.
听上去吓得屁滚尿流.
Sounded like something
scared the shit out of him.
他想找你，我说我会安排
He said he had to talk to you.
I said I'd see what I could do, Val.
他没说是什么事？
Y eah? Did he tell you
what it was about?
他说林恩死了.
He said to tell you Lynn was dead.
他说有个家伙放话要找你
He said some guy came around
talking mean and wanted you.
他没说别的.我只想让你知道
And that's all he said.
I thought you ought to know.
做得好，我会去找那个婊子养的
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you did right.
I wanna talk to that son of a bitch.
谁？史泰曼吗？
Who, Stegman?
还尼克森总统吗?
当然是史泰曼
No, President Nixon.
Of course Stegman.
叫他到桥下的瓦里克酒吧等我
T ell him Varrick's by the bridge.
这样吧...
Make it...
二十分钟后, 知道吗?
Make it 20 minutes, huh?
- 史泰曼.
- 瓦尔.
-Steggie.
-Hey, Val.
你知道,我一直想和你联系
You know, I tried to call you,
不过你好像换了号码了,我找不到你
but you must have changed your
number again. 'Cause I got nothing.
我从来没有给你过我的固定电话,史泰曼
I never gave you
my original number, Steg.
那个家伙长什么样
What did this guy look like?
嗯,他有黑头发,蓝眼睛
Well, he had, like, dark hair, blue eyes.
长的象克鲁马努人一样发育不全.
He was like
a real Cro-Magnon-looking bastard.
那么,林恩死了 就有人来找事,是吧?
Well, if Lynn's dead,
maybe he did us a favor, huh?
我知道你什么意思
我不是希罕这一千块钱
I know what you mean, except
I'm out like a grand a month, you know?
是啊我们可以协商解决
Well, maybe we can
work something out.
你有那人的名字吗?
Did you get a name?
他说他叫波特
He said his name was Porter.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 他说他为了波特而来
- 不,不是,他说他叫波特
-He said he was there for Porter?
-No. No, he said he was Porter.
我要跟你老实说
Yeah. I'll tell you something.
我不想让那家伙盯着我,你要理解我
I wouldn't want that guy after me, either.
I know how you must feel.
我是谁?无名氏吗?
What am l, a nobody?
- 不是.
- 我有手下.
-No.
-I've got friends.
只要我吩咐一声
All I have to do is point.
拿起电话，说出他的名字，他就死定了
I pick up a phone, say his name,
and he's a dead man.
这次他活不了！
And this time he stays dead!
好好，瓦尔，冷静
好吗?
All right, Val, try to keep it down.
All right?
别激动.
It's okay.
- 他提到我什么？
- 没什么
-What did he say about me?
-He just... Nothing.
- 他说你欠他钱.
- 没说别的吗？
-He just said you owed him money.
-Not why? Nothing else?
没有.
Nothing.
- 怎么?你欠他多少？
- 不关你的屁事
-Why? How much you owe him?
-None of your goddamn business.
呃，我想...
Well, I just, you know...
我只是觉得他想杀你
I got the feeling
he'd like to kill you, that's all.
天啊
Oh, Christ.
波特
Porter.
什么?
What?
你跟他都说了什么？
What did you tell him?
没有. 我能说什么？
Nothing. What could I tell him?
你告诉他，那笔钱，海洛因
You tell him about the money?
The heroin?
都在他手上
He had it with him.
我只说货是我送的.
I just... I told him I delivered it.
- 没说别的吗？
- 我什么也不知道
-You didn't tell him nothing else?
-I don't know nothing else.
不，你跟他说什么了
Nah. You gave him something.
你一定招出名字让他来找我
A name, maybe.
Someone who knows where to find me.
- 我向我老母发誓...
- 去你老母!
-I swear, Val, on my mother...
-Hey, fuck your mother!
骂人就不好了，冷静点
Hey, that's not nice.
Now, why don't you try to take it easy?
- 看什么看？
- 冷静
-What the fuck you looking at?
-Take it easy.
瓦尔别这样
不要闹事了
Val, don't. Come on. Not again.
Don't do that.
- 你他妈看什么看？
- 瓦尔，拜托你，别闹事
-What the fuck you looking at?
-No, Val, no. Come on. Not again.
- 你他妈看什么看？
- 瓦尔，拜托你，别闹事
-What the fuck are you looking at?
-Val, come on, don't. Not again.
- 快点住手
- 有问题吗？
-Come on, just forget it.
-ls there some trouble here?
没有，你知道，呃...
我们正要走
No, you know what? We're...
We're just... We're leaving.
马上走
We're leaving.
这样吧，瓦尔，我请客
You know what, Val?
This one's on me, okay?
难道要我掏钱请客吗？
You see me reaching
for my fucking wallet?
不.
No.
- 老兄，迈克尔在吗？
- 他在那里
-Hey, pal, is there a Michael here?
-That's him over yonder.
迈克尔
Michael.
听说你认识高级应召女郎
I'm told you're the man to see
about expensive horizontal refreshment.
我在找一位叫萝丝的女孩
I'm looking for a girl named Rosie.
召妓是违法的,
你说什么我不懂
Prostitution is illegal,
and you're speaking Greek.
这种事通常要低调一点
Usually these matters are conducted
with more discretion.
这样够低调吗？
Be discreet now.
- 她叫什么？
- 萝丝
-What was her name again?
-Rosie.
谁要找她？
And who should I say is looking for her?
打给她就是了
Just call her.
- 萝丝？
- 是我
-Rosie?
-Yeah.
电话给我
Give me the phone.
拿着
Here.
拿好你的钱.
Take care of that.
- 萝丝？.
- 你是什么人？
-Rosie.
-Who the hell is this?
- 波特
- 少来，波特死了
-Porter.
-Try again, honey. Porter's dead.
我以前是你的司机兼保镖
I used to drive for you,
provide a safe work environment.
波特？
Porter?
嗯.
Yeah.
嗨.
Hi.
快进来
Come on. Come in.
你这死人气色挺好的
You look pretty good for a dead guy.
- 你怎么听说的？
- 有人在放话.
-How'd you hear about it?
-People who know were talking.
我也听说你老婆也自己回来了
Plus, I heard
your wife was back in town alone.
她死了
She's dead.
很遗憾，波特
I'm sorry, Porter.
为什么？
Why?
天啊，你还是没变
你还是一样冷酷无情
Jesus. Surly Porter.
You're the same as ever, aren't you?
这不像你的作风
This doesn't look like you.
人都会改变
Yeah, well, people change.
不要动，没关系
Stay. It's okay, baby. It's okay.
没关系，宝贝，好的
Come on, sweetheart. It's okay.
这是世上最悍的狗
Meet the nastiest damn dog
who ever lived.
- 叫什么？
- 波特
-What's his name?
-Porter.
你走后，它负责保护我
He took your job after you left.
跟你一样狠，只是不会离开我
He's just as tough,
but he won't leave me, will you, baby?
我要你帮忙
I need a favor.
帮忙？
A favor?
也许你真的变了
Maybe you're not the same as ever.
我找地下组织的人
I'm looking for a syndicate boy.
那是黑道，已没人说地下组织
It's the outfit, baby.
We don't say syndicate anymore.
你知道我什么意思。随你怎么说
Well, you know what I mean.
Whatever the hell you call it.
别生气，波特
他叫什么？
Don't get touchy, Porter.
What's his name?
瓦尔雷斯尼克
Val Resnick.
那狗娘养的
Oh, that son of a bitch.
- 你认识他？
- 没错
-You know him?
-Yeah.
几年前见过面
I met up with him once a few years ago.
他喜欢毒打应召女郎
He can't use Star Service anymore
because he beats up all the girls.
差点打死一个
He almost killed one.
就是你？
You?
重要吗？你丢下我不管
Does it matter?
You quit looking after me, remember?
你知道他在哪儿吗？
Would you happen to have a line
on where he might be?
- 我想他住在旅馆吧？
- 哪一家？
-I suppose he's at the hotel.
-Which one?
黑道住的旅馆，他们都住那.
The outfit hotel. They're all there.
你有地址吗？
You got an address?
我们是朋友，对吧？
We're friends, right?
至少以前是
I mean, we used to be.
我现在也是黑道手下
But I'm an employee, too,
我想他们不喜欢我告诉你
and I don't think
the outfit would like me telling you
旅馆在哪里
where the hotel was, would they?
- 肯定，你认为我会干嘛
- 你有多强悍，波特？
-No. What do you think I'm gonna do?
-How strong are you, Porter?
我认为你是世上最强悍的人
Personally, I think you are
the strongest man I have ever met.
不过这还不够
But I wonder if it's enough.
为什么？
For what?
你一定是想找他麻烦
If I know you, you want this Resnick guy
for something he won't like.
对，我要杀他
Yeah, I'm gonna kill him.
他不会喜欢的
That's something he won't like.
要是你没干好被抓到
What if something goes wrong,
and they grab you
他们问你消息是谁说的
and they ask you
where you found out about the hotel?
这个你不用担心
我不会把你招出来
Why are we even talking about this?
You know I wouldn't turn you in.
我不会招出来是谁说的
I wouldn't talk about who told me what.
如果他们会对你严刑拷打呢
But what if they ask you hard?
我就说是计程车行的史泰曼
I'll tell them it was a cab dispatcher
named Stegman.
橡木旅馆，联合街和十七街路口
The Oakwood Arms, Union and 1 7th.
直到现在，你都故意没问我的情况
All this time, you don't even pretend
to ask how I've been.
现金还是其他的？
You need any cash or anything?
你去死吧，混蛋
我会跟他说你来的
Get yourself killed, prick.
I ought to tell him you're coming.
你好，瓦尔
Hi, Val.
钱呢？
Where's my money?
不在那儿，你的枪在这儿
No, it's not there. I took your gun.
It's back here.
你看起来像个男妓
You look like a pro.
你乖乖闭嘴，就能活着走出去
You keep your mouth shut,
and you'll walk out of here.
我的七万，我要讨回
My 70 grand, I want it.
已经不在我这里
I don't have it right now.
在哪里？
Where is it?
我把十三万都给了黑道
I gave all $130,000 to the outfit.
I gave it all to them.
跟他们说那不是你的钱
Well, tell them you gave them
money that doesn't belong to you,
去要回来
and get it back.
办不到，波特，你不知道这些人...
Now, Porter, I can't do that.
I mean, you don't know these...
不管怎样你都会杀我
You're gonna kill me
whether I get the money or not.
好吧，我去拿钱
All right, I'll get it. I'll get it.
I'll get the money.
给我几天的时间，好不好？
Just give me a few days, all right?
你在干嘛？
What the fuck are you doing?
明天中午，快答应
Noon. Tomorrow. Say it.
好吧
All right.
拜托你，波特原谅我吧
我是不得已的，你应该了解
You know, this may sound crazy, Porter,
but no hard feelings, huh?
你会感激我所做的
I did what I had to do.
You could appreciate that.
我能够了解
你个婊子养的
Yeah, I appreciate that,
you son of a bitch.
不，不，别
No, no, no. Don't.
请，让我来
Please. Allow me.
天啊，上帝
Jesus. God.
上帝
God.
臭婊子！
You bitch!
让她干活
Let her work.
我爱你，宝贝
Me love you, baby.
我要好好地玩你
Me love you long time.
不，等一下
Wait up, hon. Wait.
明天. 中午
Tomorrow. Noon.
你把钱带到第七街和富兰克林街口
You and the money, be at the corner
of 7th and Franklin at the pay phone.
好，好
Okay. Okay.
这是哪儿来的？
Where'd you get this?
一个妓女的架子上
Some hooker had it on her shelf.
我认出你，所以偷偷拿走
I recognized you.
I swiped it in case I could use it.
你有打她吗？
Did you hurt her?
你有打那妓女吗？
The hooker, did you hurt her?
什么跟什么吗？
What does that have to do
with anything?
我有几分钟空档
I've got a few minutes.
去煮蛋吧
So go boil an egg.
需要效劳吗？
Can I help you?
瓦尔雷斯尼克.
我和卡特先生约好了
Val Resnick.
I got an appointment with Mr. Carter.
好的
Yes.
转过身去
Turn around, please.
听着，伙计，你没必要这么干
Listen, sweetie,
you don't have to do that.
转身
Turn around.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 很好
- 你喜欢吗?
-Very nice.
-You like that?
- 下面.
- 是的.
-It's down there.
-Yes.
这么说你来者不善啊
This isn't how
Mr. Carter likes his visitors.
我知道.
I know.
我是惹上麻烦了才这样.
It's just I'm in a little bit of trouble
right now.
是的，卡特先生也这么认为
Yes, Mr. Carter thinks so, too.
这边请.
This way, please.
菲利浦说你惹上麻烦需要帮忙
Philip tells me you have a problem
you need help with.
是的，老大
Yes, sir.
就是昨晚闯进旅馆的家伙？
Is it your problem who breached
our security last night at the Oakwood?
是的，老大
Yes, sir.
他闯进我房间...
Then he breaks into my apartment...
我们有3个方法可以搞定这事
There's three ways
that we can handle this.
一，我们可以帮你
One, we can help you.
二，我们让你自生自灭
Two, we can allow you to help yourself.
三呢，我们把你做掉
And three, we can have you replaced.
我们在你身上做了投资，雷斯尼克
We have an investment in you, Resnick.
所以帮你可以说是保护投资
So assisting you would be,
in a way, protecting our investment.
这一向是我们最好的政策
And that is always
good business policy.
是的，老大，卡特先生
谢谢你，你不会后悔的
Yes, sir. Yes, sir, Mr. Carter.
Thank you, sir. You won't regret it.
现在,
Now,
菲利浦说有人想杀你？
according to Philip,
a man has come to town to kill you?
是的，老大
Yes, sir.
据你说他是个职业抢匪，只有一个人
And you say that he's alone
and that he's a professional robber.
是不是?
Is that correct?
是的. 他抢薪水和银行，天生坏胚子
Yes, sir. He does payroll jobs, banks,
you know, stuff like that.
- 他叫什么？
- 波特
-What's his name?
-Porter.
呃，名字是什么？
Well, what's his first name?
这个我不知道
You know, I don't know it.
他自称波特外没别的名字了
He never called himself
anything but Porter.
那十三万是哪儿来的？
Where did you get the $130,000?
他为这笔钱来城里找你？
That's why
this man has come to town, huh?
为了你还我们的十三万？
The $130,000 that you paid us back?
是的，老大，只有七万是他的
Yes, sir, but only $70,000 of it was his.
又没问你钱的来路
Well, we never asked you
where you got the money.
这与我们无关
It was none of our business.
不过现在似乎与我们有关了
But now it appears
it has become our business.
他的档案，卡特老大
Here's his file, Mr. Carter.
你知道你对组织的用处吗？雷斯尼克？
Do you understand your value
to the organization, Resnick?
你丧尽天良，这迟早有用
You're a sadist. You lack compunction.
That comes in handy.
不过现在你却让个人的私事
But now you've allowed an area
of your personal life
危害到组织
to become a danger to us.
我们要的是坚强独立的手下
A man in our organization
needs to be tough and self-reliant.
如果你能自己解决问题
Were you to handle this problem
on your own,
毫无疑问地
there would be no doubt
你就符合我们的要求
that you're the kind of man we want.
我想解决问题
I want to.
- 我要自己处理，卡特老大
- 太好了
-I want to handle it myself, Mr. Carter.
-Great.
在事情没结束之前
Until the matter is handled,
我要你先搬出橡木旅馆
I want you to move out
of the Oakwood Arms.
可是我没地方...
But I don't have a place...
我不能再让旅馆出事
I don't want any more unpleasantness
at the hotel.
是的，老大
Yes, sir.
瓦尔丢尽了颜面，斯派德
That's it. Val's in the doghouse, Spider.
我建议我们另谋他路
I'll fill you in on the way.
他喜欢我，我们走吧
He loves me. Let's go.
他不顶你，瓦尔
He doesn't love you, Val.
对不起，我们另有任务
Sorry. We've been reassigned.
无所谓
Go ahead.
昨晚到现在，没有你们我一样很安全
看着我，看看
After last night, I'm safer without you.
Look at me. Look at this.
好的不得了
What the fuck good are you, huh?
滚
Get out of here.
我不会忘了你们的逼脸的
Never forget a pussy's face,
you remember that.
我自己解决
I'll do it myself.
我自己解决。你要想干得好
Do it myself. You want it done right!
就得亲自动手！
You got to do it yourself!
这就是美式作风！
It's the American way!
- 喂？
- 你的朋友来了吗？
-Yes?
-Did your friends make it to town?
来了，昨晚就来了
Oh, yeah. Last night, baby.
你有说波特抢走他们的钱吗？
Good. Now, did you tell them
it was Porter took that payroll?
说了. 而且他们要报仇了
I did. And they want retribution.
很好，就这么办吧
All right. All right. Here's what we do.
糟糕.
Oh, shit.
该死.
Shit.
下次你死定了
Next time, Porter.
看来波特交了新朋友
Looks like Porter's
made some new friends.
- 小心点
- 我没事，我不告他们
-Easy, mister.
-I'm okay. I don't want to press charges.
- 他们是谁？
- 不晓得，没关系
-Who were they, pal?
-I don't know. I don't know.
我很好，我不想...
原来是你们
All right. I don't wanna...
Oh, it's you guys.
史泰曼说你能弄到一大笔钱
Our buddy Stegman says you got a line
on a load of cash there, Porter.
整整二十五万
250 grand, to be exact.
七万
70.
- 拜托，老兄，别碰我
- 好的，好的.
-Come on, man. Get off of me.
-All right, all right, all right.
你把我们当白痴吗？
What do you take us for, huh? ldiots?
没有人会为了七万这么做
Nobody'd go through all this shit
for 70 grand.
我们不喜欢麻烦，伙计
We don't like trouble, buddy.
但你是个大麻烦
You look like a whole bunch of trouble
to us.
有具女尸吸食海洛因
We found a dead girl full of heroin.
现场有争斗的痕迹,
There were signs of a struggle,
验尸官不确定是吸毒过量致死
and the coroner's not so sure
it was an OD.
有个目击证人
We got a witness, though.
只剩一个鼻孔
记得他吗？
A guy with only one nostril.
Remember him?
嗯
Yeah.
别怕，波特，我们会罩你
Hey, don't worry, Porter.
We're gonna give you immunity.
让你作案，不怕坐牢
Room to operate,
"Get Out of Jail Free" card.
你只要把钱给我们
All you got to do is get the money.
我们不能帮忙
Oh, we can't help you, though.
- 那是犯法的
- 懂了吗？波特？
-lt'd be against the law.
-You understand, Porter?
- 那是我的钱
- 错了,波特.
-It's my money.
-Wrong, Porter.
操!
Fuck!
那是我们的钱
我和我伙伴的
It's our money, Porter.
Me and my partner's money.
你乖乖听话就能分一份
You be a good boy,
we'll give you a piece.
很容易的，波特
It will be easy, Porter.
懂不懂？
You got it?
- 他懂啦
- 懂吗？
-Yeah, he's got it.
-You understand?
保重，再联络
You take it easy, huh? We'll be in touch.
好，谢了
Sure, thanks.
蠢蛋
Fuck.
天啊，你得去看医生
Jesus Christ, Porter,
you need to see a doctor.
是.
Yeah.
- 会有点痛
- 尽管清洗伤口，好吗？
-It's gonna sting.
-Just clean it up, all right?
- 按住
- 好，没问题
-You hold it there.
-Yeah, right.
让我来
I'll do it.
告诉我，波特
Tell me something, Porter.
你在我们上床那晚决定走的吗
When did you decide to leave?
Was it that night we slept together?
不是
No.
是在隔天开车送你的路上
It was the next day
when I had to drive you to work.
你可以叫我不干
You could have asked me to quit.
你也可以叫我送你到别处
You could have asked me to drive you
somewhere else.
Hubba, hubba, hubba.
谢了
Thanks.
- 合身吗？
- 当然
-Does it fit?
-Oh, yeah.
好像是量身订做的
Like it was made for me.
穿着进棺材很帅
lt'll look great in your casket.
你知道吗？
You know what I think?
我觉得你死的谣言是真的
I think that all those stories
about you being dead were true.
你只是不肯承认
You're just too thick-headed to admit it.
波特，我好想你
Porter. God, I missed you.
我好想你
I missed you.
- 别说话
- 不，我...
-Don't talk. Don't.
-Oh, no, l...
不行，我有...
I can't. I got...
事情要做
Stuff to do. I got...
波特
Porter.
他人呢？
Where is he?
波特在哪儿？
Porter. Where is he?
他在卧室
He's in the bedroom.
他伤得重吗？
Is he hurt bad?
医生马上就到
The doctor should be here any minute.
胡说八道
No. That's bullshit.
我来了，老友
Porter, here I come, pally.
波特!
Porter!
该死
Goddamn!
给我过来!
Get in there!
- 他人呢？
- 他走了!
-Where is he?
-He's gone!
他走了，他走了
He's gone. He's gone.
走了吗？
Gone, huh?
我认得你，你是照片上的妓女
I know you.
You're that whore from the picture.
没错.
Yeah.
你怎么会认识他？
How do you know him?
他以前替我开车
He used to drive me.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
我现在要替你开苞
I'm driving you now, honey.
- 你知道你是什么吗？
- 告诉我呀
-You know what you are?
-Educate me.
好.
Okay.
你是专门打女人的臭猪
An ugly pig who beats up women
on account he can't get it up
你的胆量跟那话儿一样小
'cause he's too terrified
of his own fucking shadow!
- 是吗？
- 是！
-ls that right?
-Yep!
- 是吗？
- 是！
-ls that right?
-Yeah.
我猜你今天一定很走运
Then I guess you must be the lucky girl.
我要把你操得不成人形
Sweetie, I am gonna fuck you
six ways from Sunday.
天！
Jesus.
我忘了拿香烟
Forgot my cigarettes.
妈的.
Shit.
那么，瓦尔.
All right, Val.
这个黑道组织，无所谓叫啥了
This syndicate, or outfit
or whatever the hell you call it,
一定有个头儿，是吧？
it's got a head man, right?
是谁？
Who is it?
他们会宰了我，波特
They'll kill me, Porter.
你以为我不敢杀你吗？
现实点
What do you think I'm gonna do to you?
Worry about me.
该死!
Goddamn!
说出名字，快点
Names. Come on.
斐法斯和卡特
Fairfax and Carter.
斐法斯和卡特在这里是老大
They run the whole city.
斐法斯和卡特
Fairfax and Carter.
他们在哪里？
Where do I find them?
斐法斯现在不在城里
Fairfax isn't in town right now.
卡特呢？他在吗？在哪里？
What about Carter? Where is he?
Is he in town?
找他也没有用
Porter, it won't do you any good.
他们会.. 天! 你...
They're gonna... Jesus! You...
弗里德里克卡特投资公司
商业大道120号
Frederick Carter lnvestments.
120 Commerce Avenue.
谢了.就这样.
Hey, thanks. There they are.
好吧. 好吧!
All right. All right!
我愿意帮你
I'll help you out.
你是个疯子，为了七万甘愿卯上黑道
You're fucking nuts going up
against the outfit for 70 grand,
- 不过我帮你
- 哦?
-but I'm gonna help you out.
-Yeah?
来，继续说
Here. Keep talking.
谢了. 我...
Thanks. l...
那里防守严密，我带你进去
I can get you in there.
Place is tighter than a drum.
- 有几名守卫？
- 不过，呃...
-How many guys in there?
-But, well...
多得数不完
It's tighter than hell.
外面只有一个
They got only one guy
on the outside, though,
我带你绕进去
so I got a way around...
你疯了
你这个疯子够变态
You are crazy.
You are a crazy son of a bitch.
- 所以我才爱你
- 呵.
-That's why I love you.
-Yep.
- 有打火机吗？
- 我...什么?
-You got a light?
-l... What?
有火吗？
You got a light?
没有...没有...
No. No.
- 那你还有什么用？
- 等等!
-Well, then what good are you?
-Wait!
萝丝
Rosie.
租约用你的名字吗？
Is your name on the lease here?
黑道，都是黑道出的钱
The outfit.
The outfit pays for everything.
我要你收拾贵重的物品
I want you to gather everything up
that you need,
离开这地方
say goodbye to this place.
好吗?
Okay?
- 我告诉过你他会来的.
- 把那该死的钱给我.
-I told you he'd show up.
-Give me my goddamn money, please.
嗯，把钱也给我
Yeah, give me my money, too.
把那该死的钱给我.
Give me my goddamn money, please.
- 那是他吗？
- 是的，快
-Sure that's him?
-Yeah, that's him, come on.
- 非常感谢
- 谢谢.
-Thank you very much.
-Thank you.
你来说吧
Yeah, there you go.
- 怎么样了，哥们
- 我们的钱在里面
-What you up to, buddy?
-Well, our money's in there
如果你还感兴趣的话
if you're still interested.
我想要的是用钱买的船
Well, not in the dough
but the boat I'm gonna buy with it.
- 他在这儿干嘛？
- 见者有份，波特
-What's he doing here?
-It's a ride-along, Porter.
你的份越来越小了
You see, your piece of the pie
just got a little smaller.
别怕，我会留点渣给你
But don't worry,
I'll leave you some crust.
你还等什么？快去拿钱呀
去拿我们的钱
What are you waiting for, Porter?
Go get it. Go get our money.
- 帮个忙好吗？
- 我们很乐意帮忙
-You guys do me a favor?
-We're here to help, buddy.
当我进去时，我会被搜身
Well, they're probably gonna frisk me
when I go in there,
帮我保管一下
so I wonder if you wouldn't mind
holding on to this.
天啊
Jesus.
只要一会
You know, just for a little while.
好吧，波特
Sure, Porter.
好枪
Hey, nice balance.
臭小子.
Douche bag.
我能帮什么忙？
Can I help you?
- 我要见卡特先生.
- 你是谁？
-Yeah, I want to see Mr. Carter.
-And who are you?
就说是我干掉瓦尔
Tell him I'm the guy
that whacked Val Resnick.
抱歉, 我没...
I'm sorry, I don't...
我没听到，请重复
Didn't copy. Repeat.
好
Right.
卡特先生要见你，让我搜身
Mr. Carter will see you.
Turn around so I can frisk you.
你把瓦尔干掉了?
So you popped old Val, huh?
谢谢，左边口袋
Thanks. Left pocket.
- 要拿着吗
- 是的，它会帮点小忙
-Saving up?
-Yeah, every little bit helps.
跟我来
Follow me.
干得好. 坐下
Bravo. Sit down.
我要称赞你
他们2个是好手
My compliments.
They were two of my best.
不，他们都太逊了
No, they lull too easy.
48.
你想向我要什么
There's something you want from me.
瓦尔雷斯尼克给你十三万
Val Resnick gave you $1 30,000.
那是他欠我们的债
Paid us. It was a debt.
七万是我的，我要讨回来
Well, $70,000 of it was mine,
and I want it back.
抱歉，雷斯尼克跟我说过，不过我忘了你叫什么
I'm sorry. Resnick told me, but
I seem to have misplaced your name.
- 波特
- 波特，是的.
-Porter.
-Porter. Right.
我不会再忘记的
I won't forget it again.
我们不是不讲道理，波特
The outfit is not unreasonable, Porter,
不过谁也不会同意你的要求
but no corporation in the world
would agree to what you're asking.
斐法斯会还钱吗？
What about Fairfax?
Will he give me my money?
雷斯尼克真多嘴
Resnick told you quite a bit, didn't he?
斐法斯也会这么说
Fairfax will tell you
the same thing I have.
我们不能做这种决定
We're not authorized
to do things like this.
- 谁？谁能做决定？
- 委员会
-Who is? Who makes the decisions?
-Well, a committee would make
- 得投票表决.
- 不，肯定有一个人可以.
-a decision in this case.
-No, no. One man.
你已经是高层了，一定能接触那个人，谁？
You go high enough,
you always come to one man. Who?
是的, 弗里德卡特
我要和布朗森先生通话
Yeah, Fred Carter.
I wanna talk to Bronson.
对不起打扰你了，有个事...
Yeah, sorry to bother you,
but I have a problem.
有个家伙在我的办公室里拿着枪要杀了我
There's a man in my office with a gun
who says he's gonna kill me
如果组织不给他13万美金的话...
if the outfit doesn't pay him $130,000...
7万，是7万...让我和他说话
$70,000. It's 70... Let me talk to him.
她。
Her.
他想和你通话
He wants to speak to you.
免提
The speaker.
我是布朗森.
This is Bronson.
这个叫卡特的人对你值多少钱?
How much is this guy Carter
worth to you?
多少钱？你什么意思？
Worth? What do you mean?
要么我拿回我的钱，要么卡特死掉
Well, either I get my money,
or I'll kill Carter.
我不喜欢被人威胁.
I don't like to be threatened.
我不是威胁你,
我是在威胁卡特先生.
I'm not threatening you,
I'm threatening Carter.
真的?
Touche.
有胆子！你是谁？
An audacious man. Who are you?
我的钱，给不给？
My money, yes or no?
不给.
No.
卡特? 卡特?
Carter? Carter?
卡特，发生什么事了？
Carter, what's happening?
快派人去商业大道，快！
Get some people down
to Commerce street. Now.
卡特?
Carter?
说话，卡特？
Speak to me. Carter?
你还是没搞懂，你这个蠢蛋
You just don't get it, do you,
you dumb fuck?
我希望你是对他说的不是对我说.
I sure hope you're talking to him
and not me.
卡特？卡特！
Carter! Carter!
我刚把他杀了
I just croaked Carter.
我希望你能通知斐法斯，告诉他
I want you to call Fairfax
and tell him that.
自己去舔屁眼吧，混蛋.
Smoke them if you got 'em, asshole.
你活不过24小时.
You've got 24 hours left to breathe.
明天找人收尸吧.
That's one day to get
your tiny little world in order.
听到了没有，宝贝，嗯？
Do you understand that, sweetheart?
Do you?
波特，波特，波特，把钱给我
Porter, Porter, Porter, get my money.
- 我看到他了，我看到他了，我看到他了
- 赶紧，赶紧，赶紧
-I see him, I see him, I see him.
-Come on, come on, come on.
就在这里
Right here.
- 我没看到现金.
- 他们写的支票？
-I don't see any cash.
-They write you a check?
我被耍了，我得见另一个人
They gave me the run around.
I have to go and see another guy.
最后一次机会，否则我们就得找你问女尸的事
Last one, then we got a dead woman,
an assault,
所有的证据都指向你
and all kinds of stuff
to talk to you about.
需要做很多报告，波特
我们很不想处理这么多公文
That means more paperwork, Porter,
and we don't like paperwork.
真可惜，波特
别这么垂头丧气
Damn shame, Porter,
but don't let the bastards get you down.
没错，波特，别放弃
That's right, Porter. Don't give up.
- 把枪还给我
- 好
-Hey, can I have my piece back?
-Oh, yeah.
好棒的枪
重得可以当钳子用
Nice roscoe, Porter.
Heavy enough to be a nutcracker.
再联络，洛基
We'll be in touch, Rocky.
继续好好努力
Keep up the good work.
洛基? 这是啥意思?
Rocky? Where did you get Rocky from?
动画片里的一只松鼠《洛基和布温克》
Squirrel on the cartoon.
Rocky and Bullwinkle.
欢迎回来，斐法斯先生
Good to have you back in town,
Mr. Fairfax.
高兴才怪
I wish I could say I was glad to be back.
我本应今早上和海豚一起戏水
I was swimming with the dolphins
this morning.
轻点，行不？
Easy, would you?
这可是真品鳄鱼皮箱，老天，你小心点
It's genuine alligator, for God's sake.
What's the matter with you?
对不起，斐法斯先生
Sorry, Mr. Fairfax.
- 你好，斐法斯先生
- 怎么了，查理
-Hello, Mr. Fairfax.
-How's it going, Charlie?
我们和另外两个警探
Well, between us
and our neighborhood cops,
把波特盯死了
I'd say we got him
pretty well covered, huh?
华特，醒醒
Walter, wake up.
华特!
Walter!
醒醒!
Wake up!
把箱子举高，两位
Keep those bags up, boys.
- 你是什么人？
- 你为了我提早回来
-Who the hell are you?
-I'm the reason you're back early.
- 你是波特？
- 正是在下。
-You're Porter?
-That's right.
拿箱子的手要平举
Keep those bags up above
shoulder level, boys.
否则我就开枪
You drop them and I'll drill you.
怎么？你要我倒立吗？
Well, what'll you have me do,
stand on my head?
不是我要你帮我个忙
打电话给布朗森先生
No. I want you to do me a favor
and call Mrs. Bronson,
一起商量一下钱的事
see what we can do about my money.
哦，她让卡特送死
Well, she let Carter die.
那个暴牙老爹死得好
But that poor buck-toothed bastard
is probably better off dead anyway.
她或许也会让我死
She'd probably let me die, too.
不，上次她以为我在虚张声势
No, with Carter
she thought I was bluffing.
试试看
Try her.
好吧
All right.
你们两个被开除了
You two are fired.
喂? 是这样子的
Hello? Yes, it's like this.
我的客厅有个叫波特的人
I'm standing in my living room
and there's a man here named Porter
他说你迟早得付钱给他
who says that he expects you
to pay him sooner or later.
当然
Yes, of course.
- 她想跟你讲话
- 用免提
-She wants to talk to you.
-Put her on the speaker.
我是波特
This is Porter.
我想你可以干掉斐法斯
I should probably have you
just shoot Fairfax
然后我雇你替代他们.
and then hire you to run the city for me.
不过你这家伙没脑子。
Too bad you're just a punk
with the right balls-to-brains ratio.
亲爱的，我不会付你十三万
Honey, I wouldn't even
get out of bed for 1 30 grand.
你的人听错了，不是13万...
You people aren't listening.
It's not 1 30 grand...
不，你听着，你将无处可逃.
No, you listen.
You got no place to go, Porter.
你完了，明白我说的吗？
You're finished.
Do you get what I'm talking about?
斐法斯？
Fairfax?
- 你在干嘛？
- 斐法斯？
-Hey, what the hell are you doing, man?
-Fairfax?
- 你没事吧
- 没事.
-Are you okay?
-Yes. No, it's all right.
他把我的鳄鱼皮箱打穿了，给我的衣服开了个洞
He's just killing my alligator bags
and shooting holes in my suit.
- 只是说说
- 好，波特，我认输.
-Man, that's just mean.
-Okay, Porter, I give up.
在哪里把钱给你？
Where do you wanna
pick up your money?
王十字车站.
King's Cross Station.
派一个人，蓝色背包装满现金
Send one man
with a blue backpack full of cash.
我会在月台.
I'll be on the platform.
- 车站名是什么?
- 到此为止.
-What's the name of the stop?
-It's the end of the line.
你也一样，甜心.
For you, too, sweetheart.
你为了13万美元签死刑.
You just signed your own death warrant
for $1 30,000.
我不明白，这算啥？
为了原则吗？
I don't... I don't get that. What is it,
the principle or something, huh?
不，我只想要回我的钱
No, I just want my money back.
只是70
And it's only 70.
70? 你说什么，只是70?
70? What do you mean it's only 70?
7万?
Only 70,000?
该死，我的西装都不只七万
Hell, my suits are worth more than that.
听好了 “欧森雷桑德斯”号
Listen to this. "Ocean Ray Sundancer.
"真空吸水马桶. 80,000元."
"Vacuum-flush head. 80,000 bucks."
我告诉你，他肯定拿不到钱
I'm telling you, you ain't gonna have it.
- 你想打赌吗？
- 不，我才不想赌
-You wanna bet?
-No, I don't wanna bet.
我已经输了一百五
I'm out $150 already.
一百五买不了船
他最好拿到钱
$150 I'm getting my damn boat.
Better come down with something.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
希克、李瑞
Hicks, Leary,
我们是荷伦和范欧文
内务部的
we're Holland and Vanowen.
lnternal Affairs.
别找碴，我们在盯梢
You boys wanna back off?
We're on a stakeout here.
- 请你们下车
- 干什么？
-You wanna step out of the car, please?
-What for?
两位警探，你们最好下车
I think you better
step out of the car, Detectives.
- 到底是怎么回事？
- 我不知道
-What the hell's going on?
-I don't know.
这是你的警徽吗？探长？
你报失的那枚
Is this your badge, Detective?
The one you reported missing?
- 是，在哪儿找到的？
- 你在哪儿弄丢的？
-Yeah. Where'd you find it?
-Where exactly did you lose it?
这是你的吗？
Does this belong to you?
- 是波特，跟上去
- 我会跟着他
-It's Porter. Follow him.
-I got that motherfucker.
嘿.
Hey.
波特，上车
Get in, Porter.
关上车门
Close the door.
把枪放在地板上
Now set the roscoe on the floor.
慢慢来
Slow.
我要把你交给黑道换奖赏
See, I am gonna turn you in
to the outfit for a reward.
也许他们会让我加入
And maybe they'll be so impressed
that they'll ask me to join,
这样我就发达了
and I'll be on easy street.
又有医疗、牙医保险
Medical, dental.
我要亲自把你送上门
I'm just... I'm gonna walk you right in.
活捉波特
Porter on the hoof.
除非你敢乱来
Unless you get rambunctious.
我就得把你做掉..
Then I'll just have
to take care of you myself...
你不会杀我吧？
You're not gonna fucking kill me,
are you?
放开他
Let him go.
快点.
Now.
Hubba, hubba, hubba.
嘿， 波特！
Hey. Hey. Hey, Porter!
嘿!
Hey!
来啊!
Hey, come on!
嘿，帅哥，这里是装货场
Hey, handsome. This is a loading zone.
来我离开.
So move me.
当然.
So move.
你是波特?
You Porter?
转弯开到你兄弟那里.
Over there by your buddy. U-turn.
我们有新位置，进来.
We're taking a new position. Get in.
- 哪里
- 想活命就老实点
-Where to?
-Relax and you'll survive this.
把你的手放到我可以看到的地方.
下个路口左转.
Keep your hands where I can see them.
Take the next left.
我想我办过你.
You know, I think I fucked you once.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
你觉得还有第二次吗?
What do you think
the odds are on twice?
- 10分钟内在L处集合.
- 我会的.
-I'll meet you at the L in 10 minutes.
-I'll be there.
我不认为你有机会.
I don't think your odds are good.
你还有什么要说的吗？
You got anything to say?
没有，谢谢.
No, thank you.
那就老实待在这里.
Then just stay here.
别动
Don't move.
还有其他的人在这里吗？
You got any friends here
I should know about?
男厕所
You should try the men's room.
嗨
Hey.
波特？
Porter?
过来这里
Step back here. Come on.
那个人说你应该喝这个
The guy says you should drink this.
- 谁？
- 我。
-What guy?
-Me.
用右手拿
Take it in your right hand.
坐下
Sit down.
你们的枪呢？
Where's your piece?
- 午餐盒.
- 打开它
-Lunchbox.
-Open it.
关上吧
Close it.
上火车
Get on the train.
干什么...
What...
钱在这里
Here it is.
打开
Open it.
全都在这里了，13万
It's all there. 130 grand.
7万，你这个蠢蛋，打开它
It's 70, you dumb bastards. Open it.
嗨，菲尔
Hey, Phil.
天啊，他怎么做到的？
Jesus, how'd he make it?
快点！闪开！
Come on! Move it!
你觉得你可以搞定任何事，是不是？
You think you can make
everything okay, don't you?
你有多彪悍，波特？
How strong are you, Porter?
听着可能有点疯狂，不过...
You know, this may sound crazy,
Porter, but...
你不会得到的，你个..
You just don't get it, do you, you dumb...
我们星期五下手.
We'll hit them on Friday.
有人该给我颁哲学博士学位
Someone ought to give me a PhD.
你想干什么？杀了我？
What are you gonna do, kill me?
求你了，答应我
Please. Allow me.
这算什么？为了原则吗？
What is it,
the principle or something, huh?
你这死人气色挺好的
You look pretty good for a dead guy.
快点，亲爱的，我们要离开这里
Come on, baby,
we got to get you out of here.
快点，我们得走了
Come with me.
Come on, baby, we gotta go.
波特？醒醒！快点！
Come on. Porter? Come on! Come on!
波特？
Porter?
操!妈的!
Fuck! God damn it!
波特？
Porter?
哦，萝丝
Oh, Rosie.
萝丝，萝丝
Rosie. Rosie.
- 来吧
- 萝丝
-Come on.
-Rosie.
- 帮我一把.
- 你没事的
-Help me out.
-You're okay. Okay.
- 背包，背包
- 我拿到了
-Backpack. Backpack.
-I got it, I got it.
- 我要把你送到医院
- 不要去医院
-I got to get you to a hospital.
-No hospitals.
我认识个人
I know a guy.
- 医生？
- 不是
-ls he a doctor?
-No.
不是
No.
- 告诉我在哪里
- 只管开就行了，宝贝
-Tell me where to go.
-Just drive, baby.